漫威影业出品
17号预备陪审员  请报上姓名
Potential juror number 17, please state your name.
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
理查德·戴
Richard Day.
请向庭上陈述你对被告弗兰克·卡塞尔
Can you state for the court any preexisting opinion, any at all,
■
翻译：夜魔草
是否有任何已存在的看法
that you may hold for the defendant, Frank Castle?
惩罚者吗  我觉得他是个禽兽
You mean the Punisher? I think he's an animal...
翻译：夜魔草
变态  扭曲  肮脏
a sick, twisted, venal...
校对：夜魔奶
英雄  我们该把他视为英雄
Hero. That's what we should be calling him.
他做到警察不敢做的  弗兰克·卡塞尔是个
Doing the things the cops won't do, Frank Castle is a...
时间轴：毛毛姜  夜魔念
对第二修正案[持械权]的严重侮辱
A grotesque insult to the Second Amendment,
没有权威的法西斯
a fascist without the authority.
要我说  弗兰克·卡塞尔这样的人应该
If you ask me, people like Frank Castle ought to be...
后期：夜魔吉  8T     总监：夜魔奶
得到称赞  他把那些贼人
Applauded for putting all the thieves
强盗  强奸犯都送进了停尸房
and muggers and rapists in the morgue,
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
他们该去的地方
where they belong.
也让那些混蛋
Let those bastards feel scared
试试走在街上感到害怕的滋味
walking down the street for a change.
就像山姆之子[纽约杀人狂]重演
It's Son of Sam all over again.
就像伯尼·戈茨[枪击抢劫未遂者]
It's Bernie Goetz...
感觉好像唯一保护我们的只有弗兰克
It's like the only thing protecting us is Frank.
我们一家人搬来纽约  现在我们打算搬走了
I just moved my family to New York, and now we're moving out.
如果这城市里随便谁都可以杀谁
If anyone can kill anyone in this town...
这样的疯狂什么时候是个头
where does the insanity end?
律师  已有400多名
Counselors, over 400 potential
预备陪审团出了庭
jurors have come through this courtroom.
我要告诉你们
So I should tell you,
如果你们无法就
if you can't agree to move forward
选好的12名陪审员达成一致
with the 12 men and women selected,
我会让你们在此审判中都不好受
I will make this trial a living hell for all of you.
法官大人  纽约已经很多年
Your Honor, New York hasn't seen
没有出现过如此意见不一  备受关注的案子了
a trial this divisive and this public in years.
找到无偏见的陪审员实在不易
Finding an impartial jury is not easy.
人人对弗兰克·卡塞尔都有自己的看法
Everybody has an opinion about Frank Castle.
这里是纽约  尼尔森先生
It's New York, Mr. Nelson.
人人对什么事都有自己的看法
Everybody has an opinion about everything.
雷耶斯女士  检方对陪审团满意吗
Ms. Reyes, is the prosecution satisfied with its jury panel?
是的  法官大人
Yes, Your Honor.
辩护方呢  尼尔森先生
And the defense, Mr. Nelson?
是的  法官大人  我们满意
Uh, yes, Your Honor, we are.
谢天谢地
Thank Christ.
纽约市起诉弗兰克·卡塞尔一案
The trial of The People of New York v. Frank Castle
现在开庭
is now in session.
夜
魔
侠
第二季  第七集
如果让我逮到那个整理这堆文件的
If I get my hands on the worthless intern
没用的实习生
who organized these files...
那个实习生肯定也是听地检官办公室的命令行事
Oh, I'm sure that intern's just following the DA's orders.
这不算明面上的破坏行为
It's not officially sabotage,
-只是碍事  -太下贱了
- just sets it back. - It's a cheap trick.
我们有更大的问题  比如确定辩护策略
We got bigger problems. Like, locking a defense.
-姆纳坦规则依然是最佳策略  -那是什么
- M'Naghten Rule's still our best bet. - What's that?
就是精神问题辩护
Uh, the, uh, insanity plea.
两位
Whoa, whoa, guys...
我们得想办法拿下"无罪"判决
We need to buy a "not guilty" verdict.
我高中的辩论队都能证明是卡塞尔干的
My high school debate team could prove that Castle did it.
我们需要进行积极抗辩
We need an affirmative defense.
我明白  但我不确定弗兰克是疯了
Yeah, yeah, I get that, but I'm not so sure Frank is insane.
我不是医生  但我觉得他至少有点那个意思
I'm no doctor, but I'd say he's at least driven past Crazy Town.
-福吉  我说真的  -她有点道理
- Foggy, I'm serious. - She has a point.
在纽约  精神病辩护只有0.12%的开罪率
I mean, insanity only has a 0.12% acquittal rate in New York.
雷耶斯会叫来心理医生专家做证人
Reyes is just gonna call in some expert shrink witness
推翻我们的辩护
to blow our case apart.
有什么辩护可言
What case?
我们争取审判无效呢
Look, what if we...push for a mistrial?
可以争取更多时间
We get more time.
提及不许复苏  诉讼和雷耶斯与此事的牵扯
We talk about the DNR and the suits and Reyes' involvement.
把她赶出这件案子
We get her kicked off the case.
她会意料不到
She wouldn't see it coming.
如果我们现在走那条路  我们得
If we go down that road now, we gotta prove,
在法庭上证明  政府
in a court of law, that the government
有意掩盖了伏击惩罚者一事的证据
willfully hid evidence of the Punisher ambush,
而且此事与雷耶斯有关
and that Reyes was involved.
我当时在  你也在
Well, I was there and you were there.
我们不能算毫无利益纠葛
We're not exactly impartial, okay?
不管怎样  我们明天就得拿到公开声明
And either way, we need an opening statement tomorrow.
我可以先将创后应激症作为减刑因素提出
I can open with PTSD as a mitigating factor,
专注于卡塞尔的服役历史
focus on Castle's time at war.
你觉得是战争造就了弗兰克吗
So you think the war is what made Frank what he is?
我们唯一的目标是减少指控  设下先例
Our only goal is to reduce the charges and set precedent.
卡塞尔树敌很多
Castle made a lot of enemies, all right?
如果他蹲普通监狱  他与死无异
If he goes into general population, he's as good as dead.
我们得送他去个安全地方  让他得到帮助
We need to get him somewhere safe, where he can get help, and...
提出创后应激症的事就能实现这点
citing PTSD could do that.
我们都不知道卡塞尔在那边经历了什么
I mean, none of us know what Castle saw over there...
但研究表明
but research suggests that...
创后应激症会因新压力点而触发
PTSD can be triggered by new stressors.
比如痛失家人
Like losing your family.
我得去忙开庭陈述了
I need to get to work on the opening statement,
但我们得确定卡塞尔会同意
but we need to be sure Castle will get on board with this.
我尽量
Uh, I'll try.
弗兰克明确表示
I mean, Frank made it pretty clear
至少愿意跟我交流
he's willing to talk to me, at least,
只要我是一个人
just as long as I'm alone.
你真想那么做吗
Are you sure you wanna do that?
我想帮忙
Well, I wanna help.
如果我去  更可能让他开口
We have a better shot at getting him to talk if I go.
我去拿我在写的问题单
I'll grab the list of questions I was working on.
好
Okay.
凯伦
Karen...
你知道你不是非得一个人做的
You know you don't have to do this by yourself.
没事  卡塞尔不让我害怕
It's okay. Castle doesn't scare me.
或许你该怕
Maybe he should.
我能照顾好自己
I can take care of myself.
我知道  但我对福吉也会这么说
I know... but I'd be saying it to Foggy.
或是海豹突击队的人
Or a Navy SEAL.
小心点
Just watch your back.
我保证
Promise.
给你  帮帮忙  别脱本
Here you go. Just do me a favor, stick to the script.
好
Okay.
-祝我好运  -祝你好运
- Wish me luck. - Good luck.
孩子长大得真快
Grow up so fast, don't they?
弗兰克
Hi, Frank.
女士
Ma'am.
我们翻阅了很多相似案件
Um, we've been, uh, looking over similar cases...
法律先例
legal precedents, and, uh...
我们认为如果请出
we... we think it would help
你过去认识的人或许会有帮助
to bring forth someone from your past...
比如你过去的战友
maybe from your... your military unit,
能够就
someone who could, uh...
你服役情况作证的人
speak to the nature of your service.
那跟这一切有什么关系
What's that got to do with anything?
作为品格证人
Um... it's a character witness.
我们让一个了解你的人作证
Uh, we put someone on the stand who... who knows you well.
让此人谈谈你的经历
Uh, can... can speak to what you've been through.
创后应激症吗
PTSD, huh?
我们认为这对你的辩护会大有帮助
We think it would greatly help with your defense.
别那么做  那是侮辱
Don't do that. It's an insult.
很多退伍军人都有这问题
Lots of veterans experience it.
我不是说我自己  我是说对他们
I'm not talking about me, I'm talking about them.
是对他们  真正有这个问题的人的侮辱
It's an insult to them, people who are actually going through it.
我知道你想做什么  你想就那么给我定性
I know what you wanna do, you wanna sit here and label me
又一个疯子退伍老兵
just another case of some crazy-ass combat vet
完全失去了理智
who lost his mind, huh?
或许这在哪个操蛋的法庭上
Maybe that'll appeal to some shitbag jury
能引起操蛋陪审员的共鸣
in some shitbag court.
那事不是发生在战场上
It wasn't on a battlefield.
不是发生在我人生一团糟的时候
That's not when my life went to shit.
女士  你不是跟我说过
Now, ma'am, I believe that you told me
你会帮我找到答案
that you were gonna find me answers.
你是这么跟我说的  你替我找到答案了吗
That's what you said to me. Do you have anything for me or not?
-没那么简单  -你是那么想的
- Not that easy. - That what you want?
你想要简简单单
You want things to be easy?
你现在因多宗杀人案受审
You are on trial for multiple homicides
而且完全没有辩护策略
and you don't have a defense strategy in place.
你不跟我们配合
You don't cooperate with us,
我即便帮你查明是谁杀了你的家人也无所谓
it doesn't matter if I help you figure out who killed your family,
你是得不到正义的
you will never see justice.
你的余生就只能在
All you will do, the rest of your life,
监狱里发霉
is rot in a goddamn jail cell!
雷·斯库诺弗上校  我的原指挥官
Colonel Ray Schoonover. My old CO.
别用创后应激症辩护
Let's forget the PTSD defense,
但如果你需要品格证人
but if you want a character witness,
上校就足矣
the colonel, he will do.
谢谢
Thank you.
女士  你到底查没查到什么
Now, ma'am, do you have anything for me or not?
还是我应该回牢里继续发霉
Maybe I just ought to go back and rot in my goddamn jail cell?
嗯  我做了调查
Yeah. Yeah, I did some digging.
有很多东西
All right, there are huge moving parts
他们在努力掩盖
and they do not want to be seen.
我都看过了
I've already looked at all of those.
看过几百次了
I've done it a hundred times.
是啊
Sure...
但你没跟我一起看过
but you haven't done it with me.
陪审团的各位女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury.
麻烦你们想象一下
Imagine, if you will--
我是马特
Yeah, this is Matt.
我查到了线索
I found a lead.
等等
Hold on.
艾丽卡  我现在没空
Elektra, I can't do this right now.
给我们那本账本加密的人
The guy who encoded that ledger of ours?
是个变态的纽约大学教授
Some pervy NYU professor,
教亚洲研究的译码大师
master cryptographer who teaches Asian studies.
我要去把密码从他嘴里撬出来
I'm gonna go beat the cipher out of him.
-什么事  -要来吗
- Yeah. - You wanna come?
你看过地狱狂犬的取证吗
You check out these Dogs of Hell depos?
简直是胡闹
Might as well have been written in crayon.
我觉得我们可以戳出些漏洞来
I think we could poke some holes in these.
太好了  稍等一下
That's great. Yeah. Just, uh, give me a minute.
明早我们接过的最重要的案子就要开庭了
The most important case we've ever handled starts in the morning.
我不能跟你一起去
I can't go with you.
-不能还是不想  -不能
- Can't or won't? - Can't.
不是你每次一打电话  我就得停下我的生活
My life doesn't stop every time you call.
这或许是我们翻译账本的唯一机会
This may be our one chance to translate this ledger
否则日本黑帮可能会调整部属
before the Yakuza adjust their plans
我们取得的进展就都白费了
and we lose all the progress we've made.
你在生气
You're infuriating.
当面说  两小时后  巴克莱和教堂街街口
Tell me in person. Two hours. Barclay and Church.
我知道我的品位有些变态  但下次  我保证
I know I'm into some sick shit, but next time, I swear,
我只想在你们身上吃蘑菇鸡片
all I wanna do is eat moo goo gai pan off your bodies.
吃一天
All day.
我们不是中国人
We're not Chinese.
无所谓  我看都一样性感
Whatever, it's all hot to me.
What?
干什么
He's a repulsive asshole.
他就是个恶心的混蛋
A repulsive asshole who pays well.
花钱豪爽的恶心混蛋
I can't tell any of you apart,
but I guarantee...
我分不出你们来  但我保证
I know all your tongues
better than you do.
我比你们还会说你们的语言
所以  客气点
So... be nice.
出去
Get out.
亲爱的  我回来了
Hey, honey, I'm home.
你好不乖啊
And you've been awfully naughty.
你最好别动
You're gonna wanna stay real still.
你们想要什么
What the hell do you want from me?
日本黑帮雇佣过你
You were hired by the Yakuza.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你为他们加密了文件
You encrypted files for them.
肯定付了你一大笔钱
Money must be good.
不是很多教授都能住这么豪华的高楼公寓
Not many professors can afford garish, high-rise flats
走马灯似的享用妓女
and a revolving door of prostitutes.
你们想要我做什么
What do you want me to do?
做你最擅长的事  菲利普  翻译
What you do best, Philip. Translate.
但这次是为我们翻译
But this time for us.
我要是开口他们会杀了我的
They will kill me if I tell you anything.
你不开口  我们叫你求死不得
And if you don't, we'll make you beg for killing.
30楼啊  菲利普
Thirty stories up, Philip.
你会摔成一滩肉泥的
You'd make a mighty good mess.
我猜液体会比固体还多
More liquid than solid, I'd imagine.
-怎么样  教授  -求你们  别...
- What do you say, Professor? - Come on, please...
求你  求你
Please... please.
-我给你们钱  怎么都行  -再来
- I'll pay you, I'll do anything. - Once more.
不行啊  他们会杀了我的
I can't. I can't, they'll kill me.
要碎了
It's gonna break.
好吧  好吧
Okay! Okay, shit!
停手  我翻  我翻
Stop! I'll do it! I'll do it!
我帮你
I'll help you.
好吧  乖乖的  告诉我们怎么看最后一页
All right, be a pet and tell us how to read this last page.
他们想要无法破解的密码
They wanted a code that couldn't be hacked.
我把日文片假名
I put the Japanese alphabet...
进行了编译
through a cipher.
好了
Now...
把字放进矩阵里就可以破译了
put the characters through the matrix, you can decode it all.
你来
You do it.
是每周货运
There's weekly shipments.
下一批是今晚11点
Next one is tonight at 11:00.
是湾脊铁路站场
Bay Ridge Rail Yard.
找到这个号码的货车车厢
You find a boxcar with that number...
就能找到你想找的列车
and you can find the train you're looking for.
他们运的是什么
What are they shipping?
没写  我发誓
It doesn't say, I swear.
我发誓  我帮不了你们别的了
I swear! I can't help you anymore.
多谢帮忙  教授
Well, thank you for your help, Professor.
帮你自己个忙  找更好的生意伙伴
Do yourself a favor. Find better business partners.
杀了你的装修师
And kill your decorator.
饿了吗
Hungry?
不  我觉得我再也吃不下了
No. I don't think I'm ever gonna eat again.
一整天看这些的下场
Cost of looking at these all day.
嗯  来点新鲜咖啡吧
Yeah. How about some fresh coffee?
好
Yes.
马特呢
Uh, where's Matt?
我以为他会跟你一起开夜车呢
I thought he'd be burning the midnight oil with you.
我...他...
I... He's, um...
他在修改他的开庭陈述
He's working on his opening statements.
你...跟卡塞尔谈了吗
Did you... you talk to Castle?
是的
Yeah, um...
他不肯采纳创后应激症的说法
He, uh, won't endorse PTSD, so...
该死
Oh, shit!
他并没有受战争回忆的影响  福吉
He's... he's not having war flashbacks, Foggy.
事情不是那样的
It... it's just not the truth.
卡塞尔说什么我们可用的了吗
Did Castle say anything that we can use?
等法官明天传唤首名证人的时候
'Cause when the judge calls his first witness tomorrow,
我目前唯一的计划就是逃跑
my only plan so far is to run away, and...
然后去开家肉店
open a butcher shop.
我跟弗兰克一起翻阅了我们的一些文件
Well... I, uh, went over some of our files with Frank.
他家人被杀后的尸检报告
The medical examiner's report from his family's murder,
写报告的是一位
it's filled out by a, um...
-格莱格里·塔普医生  -是的
- Dr. Gregory Tepper. - Yeah.
他是首席验尸官
He's the chief medical examiner.
他要为雷耶斯作证的
He's scheduled to testify for Reyes.
他的报告显示
Well... his report says that
丽莎  小弗兰克和玛丽亚·卡塞尔
Lisa, Frank, Jr. And Maria Castle
都是被一枪击毙
each were killed by a single gunshot,
但弗兰克说  他们当时身中数枪
but Frank says there were multiple wounds.
他的描述非常详细可怕
He describes them in awful detail, um...
各种角度
different angles, uh...
子弹口径  比手枪大的出口伤
bullet calibers, exit wounds that are too big for a handgun.
他一家人几乎被打成碎片
I mean, his family was practically shredded.
这里不一致  这是好事  但
There's a discrepancy, which is good, but...
依然是他们与弗兰克各执一词
it's still their word against Frank's,
而他当时也头部中枪
who was also shot in the head.
好吧
Okay.
你想象一下
Just for a minute...
假如你是弗兰克·卡塞尔
try... try to be Frank Castle.
你的动力完全
To be solely fueled by...
来自那么几个瞬间
by a single cluster of seconds.
你这一生中的一个时刻
One moment in... in your entire life...
每次你闭上眼睛  那一刻又浮现眼前
And every time you close your eyes, you relive that moment.
每次你睁开眼睛时  能得到
And every time you open them, you find only the...
很短暂的片刻安宁  然后就会意识到
the briefest peace before you realize that
那噩梦都是真的
that nightmare is real.
一切都未改变
That nothing has changed.
你的家人不会复活
Your family isn't coming back.
于是他们的死
And so you watch them die...
在你眼前再次重现
all over again right in front of you.
这不是弗兰克·卡塞尔曾经的经历
We're not talking about something that happened to Frank Castle,
他现在也在经历这一切
we're talking about something that is happening to him.
我明白
I hear you.
但是
But...
除非把他的家人开棺验尸
short of having his family's bodies exhumed...
我们不能证明弗兰克的说法
we still have no proof that what Frank is saying is the truth.
好吧  那么
Okay, so...
就算法医的报告被篡改了
Let's say the ME's report... was doctored.
这依然偏离主题  不能作为证据
It's still tangential and, so far, inadmissible.
怎么了
What?
除非我们能让法医
Unless we can get this ME
在证人席上证实弗兰克的说法
to corroborate Frank's story on the stand.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
机会不大  他很可能还是她的人  但
It's a long shot. He's still probably in her pocket, but...
如果成功了
if it works...
或许我们能揭发雷耶斯
maybe we expose Reyes
就能得到你祈祷的审判无效了
and we get the mistrial you've been praying for.
审判还有几小时就开始了
So, trial starts in a few hours,
抛开一个中弹的脑袋
and in lieu of a bullet-damaged brain,
我们的案子要靠一名不干净的法医
our case hinges on getting a dirty medical examiner
在证人席上招供
to crack on the stand.
那我去打给马特  把消息告诉他
Guess I'll call Matt. Give him the news.
我来吧
Oh, I'll do it.
既然是他来做年度开庭陈述
As long as he has the opening statement of the year, I'd...
我们或许还有希望
I think maybe we have a chance.
我们该赌赌日本黑帮在出口什么
We should make bets on what the Yakuza are exporting.
一百块赌野生动物
Hundred bucks says exotic animals...
或者山寨包包
or counterfeit purses.
上次他们运东西进城
Last time these guys brought something into town,
是一艘货船运一个孩子
it was a cargo ship transporting a kid.
-人口贩卖吗  -类似吧
- Human trafficking? - Yeah, something like that.
艾丽卡
Elektra.
这些车厢都是空的  这个里面有东西
All these cars are empty. This one's full.
后面的那些也是
So are the others beyond it.
装了什么
Full of what?
我不知道
I don't know.
完全装满了
There's no negative space.
货物是一堆的  没有具体形状
Cargo is uniform. There's no real shape.
但有很多
There's a lot of it, though.
足以压弯轨道了
Enough to buckle the tracks.
没错  就是这个
You're right. This is ours.
来吧  我们看看
Come on, let's go. Let's have a look.
-土  -他们知道我们来了吗
- Dirt. - Do they know we're here?
这是诱饵吗
Is this a decoy?
等等
Wait.
-他们来了  -走
- They're coming. - Let's go.
没事吧
You okay?
生命中最美好的事物都让你无法呼吸  是吧
The best things in life leave you breathless, right?
很高兴你那么想  我有东西给你
I'm glad you feel that way, 'cause I got something for ya.
今天你走运
It's your lucky day.
你怎么才来
What the hell took you so long?
受伤了吗
You hurt?
我看看
Let me see.
你说这个会落疤吗
Do you think this one will scar?
不都落疤吗
Don't they all?
看来我再也不能剪短发了
I suppose I'll never have short hair again.
你可以跟人说你是打日本黑帮时落下的嘛
Well, you could always tell people you got it fighting the Yakuza.
反正没人会信的
No one would believe you anyway.
-好了  -谢谢
- All right. - Thank you.
我们是好搭档  马修
We make a good team, Matthew.
压住
Keep some pressure on it.
你跟人怎么说
What do you tell people?
什么
About?
你的疤都哪来的
Where you got your scars?
幸好我要穿西装上班  所以
Lucky me, I wear suits to work, so...
很少有人问起
rarely comes up.
那你怎么跟你带回家的女人说
What do you tell the women you bring home?
她们都乐得忘乎所以了
Well, they're enjoying themselves too much.
不会提问的
They don't ask.
好吧
Sure.
你流血了
You're bleeding.
-没事吧  -想伤我这点可不够
- That okay? - It takes a lot more to hurt me.
你呢  就不一样了...
You, on the other hand...
这个是新的
I haven't seen this one.
是啊  俄国人喜欢用刀
Yeah, the Russians like their knives.
至少我觉得是俄国人
At least, I think it was the Russians.
这俩呢
And these?
日本黑帮
The Yakuza.
其实  是一个叫信的忍者
Actually, a ninja named Nobu.
吉冈信
Nobu Yoshioka?
怎么  你认识
What, you know him?
听说过
By reputation.
嗯  这个也是他  很疼的
Yeah, this was him, too. That hurt.
还有背后那两道
And the, uh, two on my back.
大学时还没有呢
Wasn't there in college.
大部分都是新的
Most of them weren't.
你没闲着啊
You've been busy, huh?
看来我们都是
Seems we both have.
你去哪了  艾丽卡
Where did you go, Elektra?
我们上次在一起时
The last time we were together...
尽量远离你
As far from you as I could.
你找到你想
And... did you find whatever...
寻找的东西了吗
you were looking for?
我只找到了孤独
Mostly I found that I was alone.
那你为什么不回来
Then why didn't you come back?
因为你不知道我所知道的事
Because you don't know what I know.
因为你该拥有更好的
Because you deserve better.
躺下  休息
Lie down. Get some rest.
我...真的迟到很多了
I'm, uh... I'm really late.
我会去调查货物的事
I... I will look into the exports,
看看是哪来的
see where they're coming from.
好
Yeah.
在庭上顺利  马修
Have a good day in court, Matthew.
偏偏是今天
Today, of all days...
他说过会迟到  但这也太过分了
I mean, he said he'd be late, but this is ridiculous.
福吉  他是怎么回事
Foggy, what is going on with him?
全体起立  法庭开庭
All rise. Court is now in session,
尊敬的辛西娅·巴茨法官出庭
the Honorable Judge Cynthia Batzer presiding.
案件号19864447
Indictment number 1986-4447,
纽约市诉弗兰克·卡塞尔
The People v. Frank Castle.
请坐
Be seated.
看来你们少个人
Looks like you're a man down.
陪审团的女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
被告被控多项严肃指控
the defendant has been indicted for several serious crimes.
但我要请你们  从法律角度出发
But I'm instructing you, as a point of law...
知道大学时因为压力做的梦
You know those college stress dreams,
穿着内衣去上课的那种
when you show up to your class in your underwear?
-嗯  -我现在就在经历这个
- Yeah? - That's me right now.
该死  马特该来做开庭陈述的  不是我
God damn, Matt was supposed to deliver opening, not me.
雷耶斯女士  检方可以开始做开庭陈述了吗
Ms. Reyes, are the People ready to begin opening statements?
可以了  法官大人
More than ready, Your Honor.
我们需要担心吗
Should we be worried?
马特绝不会错过庭审的啊
I mean, there's no way Matt misses this, right?
陪审团的女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury...
弗兰克·卡塞尔残忍地折磨杀害了30人
Frank Castle brutally tortured and murdered 30 people.
这些还仅是我们知道的
Thirty that we know of.
他自行执行法律
He took the law into his own hands.
自己来做法官  陪审团
Acted as judge, jury,
和最暴力的行刑者
and... most violent executioner.
你们会听到被告所杀的人都是罪犯
And you will hear that the defendant's victims were criminals...
但今天受审的不是被害人
but the victims are not on trial here today,
正义也不该握在
and justice does not belong
弗兰克·卡塞尔之流的手中
in the hands of a man like Frank Castle.
这里不是蛮荒西部
This isn't the Wild West.
正义是应该在法庭里伸张的
Justice is served here... in a court of law.
你们有责任
And it is up to each of you
从无法无天的义警手中夺回这座城市
to take back the city from lawless vigilantes...
就比如弗兰克·卡塞尔
like Frank Castle.
这人不是英雄
This man is no hero.
他是个连环杀手
He's a serial killer.
他是有罪的
And he is guilty.
谢谢
Thank you.
尼尔森先生  你可以做开庭陈述了吗
Mr. Nelson, are you prepared to make your opening statement?
-她很厉害  -你也是
- She's good. - So are you.
尼尔森先生
Mr. Nelson?
尼尔森先生  你是要行使
Mr. Nelson, are you reserving
稍后进行陈述的权利吗
the right to make your statement at a later time?
不管了
Screw it.
不  法官大人  辩方可以开始了
No, Your Honor, um... the defense is ready to proceed.
陪审团的女士们先生们
Uh, ladies and gentlemen of the jury...
被告  弗兰克·卡塞尔  不是...
the defendant, Frank Castle, is not...
抱歉
Sorry.
卡塞尔先生也是一位受害者...
Mr. Castle is as much a victim...
不  他不是
No, he's not.
好吧  那么
Okay, so...
你19岁  站在滚烫的沙地上
you're 19... standing in hot sand...
烈日当头
sun burning down...
周围一片嘈杂
noise...
嚎叫  交火
yelling, gunfire...
你唯一确定的是
The only thing that you know for sure
你被想置你于死地的敌人包围了
is that you're surrounded by an enemy that wants you dead.
但你还是要撑下去
But you do it. You endure it.
为什么
Why?
因为你有命令  有责任
Because you have orders. And you have a duty.
也因为你的生命不止步于此
And also because your life doesn't end here.
你还有爱你的人在家中等待
You have people you love waiting at home.
因为  除了是一位功勋卓著的海军陆战队队员
Because... aside from being a decorated marine...
这个男人还是个好丈夫  好父亲
the man before you is a good husband and an excellent father.
弗兰克·卡塞尔从战争地狱归来
Frank Castle returned from the hell of war
只想重拾他的生活
wanting nothing more than to pick up his life.
但他的妻子  年幼的儿子和女儿
But his wife... young son and daughter
都被罪犯残忍杀害
were brutally murdered by criminals,
却没人  警察
and no one, not the police and...
更别提地方检察官  都没有给予他帮助
certainly not the District Attorney stepped up to make it right.
弗兰克·卡塞尔没有回到家
See, Frank Castle never came home.
他从一个战场走进了另一个战场
He just traded in one war zone for another.
这场审判的重点不是义警
This trial isn't about vigilantes.
而是司法系统的失败
It's about the failure of the justice system.
而弗兰克·卡塞尔  成了掩盖
And how one man, Frank Castle, is being used as a pawn
系统失败的棋子
to cover up that system's mistakes.
检方想要见血
The prosecution wants blood.
但就像法官刚刚说的
But as the judge just said...
他们要排除一切合理怀疑
to get it, they have to prove their case
拿出证明  才能得偿所愿
beyond a reasonable doubt.
所以我今天只求各位
So all I'm asking of you today...
保持心态开放
keep an open mind.
就这样了  法官大人
That's all, Your Honor.
好漂亮的一顿鬼扯  律师
That was a pretty thick slice of bullshit there, counselor.
检方  传唤第一位证人
Prosecution, call your first witness.
是  法官大人
Yes, Your Honor.
-抱歉  -你去哪了
- Sorry, guys. - Where the hell have you been?
我是犯了个错  凯伦  我很抱歉
Look, I made a mistake, Karen, I feel terrible about it,
但福吉  我听到了一部分你的开庭陈述
but, Foggy, I caught some of your opening statement.
-你做得很好  -他做得非常棒
- You did great. - He was amazing.
多谢你支撑住了
Hey, hey, thanks for keeping us afloat, buddy.
是啊
Yeah, well...
希望雷耶斯没注意到我已经汗如雨下了
hopefully Reyes didn't notice my buckets of flop sweat.
如果地检官办公室之前没怀疑我们屁都没有
And if the DA's office didn't suspect we had nothing before,
现在肯定也开始怀疑了
they gotta be sure now.
那我们就改变这一点
Well, then we'll just have to change that.
检方明天的证人名单都有谁
Yeah, who's on the prosecution's witness list for tomorrow?
在这儿呢
Uh... I've got it, here.
塔普  太棒了
Tepper, wonderful.
雷耶斯要传唤首席法医
Reyes is calling the chief medical examiner.
刚开个好头  就突然坠入无底深渊
From rocky start to Hail Mary.
怎么  我们知道他什么
Why, what do we know about him?
我给弗兰克看了一份他家人的尸检报告
I showed Frank a copy of his family's autopsy report.
他说报告不对  而报告是塔普做的
He claims they're faked, and Tepper's name is all over them.
那很好啊
Well, that's great. All right.
-那我们让他说出来  -我们就那么想的
- So we should get him on the record. - That's what we said.
你如果来过办公室就会知道了
Which you would've known had you shown up to the office at all.
我来负责他吧  伙计
Let me take lead on it, buddy.
就像你今早那么负责吗
Like you took the lead this morning?
我明白你的意思  让我试试吧
You've made your point, all right? Let me try at least.
让我盘问一下这人
Let me get a crack at this guy.
就算我们能让虚假尸检报告纳入证据
Even if we get the false reports entered into evidence,
这还很难说  因为那是一起不相关案件中的
and it's a big "if," since they concern an unrelated crime,
这家伙自证有罪的概率太小了
odds are slim that this clown's gonna incriminate himself.
除非两个聪明的律师有办法给他下套
Unless two brilliant attorneys can figure out a way to trip him up.
-是啊  -你想来  给你了
- Exactly. - You want it? Knock yourself out.
但不费点事别指望塔普会开口
But Tepper ain't talking without a fight.
地检官在操控他
The DA's pulling his strings.
他有足够时间完善他的说法
And he's had plenty of time to bulletproof his story.
我们只有12小时瓦解他的说法
We only have 12 hours to tear it down.
我不知道我们明天之前怎么做得到
I don't know how we do that by tomorrow.
因为凯伦会把情况都告诉我
Because Karen's gonna catch me up,
我们会想到办法的
and we're gonna figure out a way.
好吧  但我要回办公室了
Fine, but I'm going back to the office,
因为我还要为余下的审判做准备
'cause I have the rest of the trial to prep for.
-你让他失望了  马特  -我知道
- You let him down, Matt. - I know. Hey, I know.
但我会弥补的
But I'm gonna make it up to him.
我也会补偿你的
And I'm gonna make it up to you.
走吧
Come on.
让塔普去想真正的报告
You get Tepper thinking about the real report.
真相  等他犯糊涂了
The real truth. And then when he's disoriented,
我在追问一句
I follow up with something like...
"是谁让你修改了报告"
"Who had you change the report?"
即便他说"没人"  也证明
And even if he says "No one," it proves--
报告是篡改过的
It proves that the report was changed.
-是的  -太聪明了
- And that's-- - That's brilliant.
瞧  你多有天赋
See? You're a natural.
近朱者赤嘛
Well, I keep good company.
知道吗
Ah, you know what?
我帮你过一遍塔普的线索问题吧
Why don't I help you go through Tepper's bread-crumb questions?
给他下套  再一举拿下
We could, you know, set 'em up, knock 'em down?
好  但会无聊的
All right, but it'll be boring.
非常无聊
And tedious.
或许要一整晚呢
Could take all night.
我不介意
Well, I don't mind.
-怎么  -你考虑过进法学院吗
- What? - You ever consider law school?
我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
福吉和我在哥大有些人脉
Well, Foggy and I know a lot of good people at Columbia.
如果你想考虑这个
I mean, if it's even something you want.
尼尔森-默多克如果变成
Just thinking Nelson and Murdock might be more fun as...
尼尔森-默多克-佩吉会更好玩
Nelson, Murdock and Page.
你真好
You're... you're sweet.
我说不好  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know
法学院是不是真适合我
if law school's really the right fit for me.
有那么多规矩和漏洞
I guess there's just something about the rules and the loopholes.
真相似乎太容易迷失
It just feels like the truth gets lost a little too often.
不会每个案件都像纽约市诉弗兰克·卡塞尔那样
Well, not every case will be The People v. Frank Castle.
嗯
Right, right.
但不仅是这一件
But, you know, it's not just this case. It's...
怎么
What is it?
我们...
You know, we...
你有...
You ever...
想过我们初遇的那一晚吗
think back to the night we first met?
经常会想
Yeah, all the time.
我坐在警察局里
While I sat in that police station...
一个人时
alone.
我惧怕这整个世界
I was afraid of the whole world.
至少  直到
Well, at least, until...
你和福吉走进我的生活
you and Foggy came into my life and...
你信任我  给了我希望
You trusted me. You gave me hope.
然后我们一起来了你家
And then we came back to your place.
我给你准备了泰国菜
I offered you Thai food.
天呐
God...
我记得那晚的一切  因为
I remember everything about that night, 'cause it's...
不是每天都会遭遇生命危险
not every day your life is threatened...
然后又被黑衣人拯救
then saved by a man in black.
你
Hey, you...
你相信他的做法吗
You believe in what he does?
就是地狱厨房的恶魔
You know, the Devil of Hell's Kitchen.
我
I, uh...
-怎么  -我相信法律
- What? - I... believe in the law.
-如果你是这个意思  -嗯  但是
- If that's what you're asking. - Right. No, but... but...
但法律没用的时候呢
But what about when the law fails?
就像在我  在弗兰克的事上那样
Like it did with me, like it did with Frank.
我们该找谁  我们该
You know, what are we supposed to turn to? What should we...
我们该相信谁来保护我们
What should we believe will protect us then?
瞧  你对一个天主教律师提这种问题
See, you're asking a Catholic lawyer.
-我  是啊  -你要我
- I, uh... Yes. - What do you...
-你指望我说什么  -我不知道
- What do you want me to say? - I don't know.
大概就是
Uh, I guess it's just...
自从我们接了弗兰克的案子
ever since we took on Frank's case, like...
我一直
I keep...
我一直问自己
I keep asking myself if there's really a difference between...
一个拯救他人和
between someone who saves lives and...
一个杜绝危险的人之间是否有区别
someone who prevents lives from needing to be saved at all.
是吧
Right?
等等
Wait... Wait a second.
弗兰克·卡塞尔应该被关起来
Frank Castle should be behind bars.
他是应该得到公正审判  但他杀人
I mean, he deserves a fair trial, but he's murdered people.
是啊  坏人
Yeah, right. Bad people.
杀他家人的人
I mean, like the ones who killed his family
来追杀我的人
or the ones who came after me.
但弗兰克不能决定谁生谁死
But it's not Frank's decision who lives or dies.
那是上帝的决定
That's up to God...
或有时候  陪审团
or sometimes a jury.
弗兰克家人的遭遇是惨剧  凯伦
What happened to Frank's family is a tragedy, Karen,
但他也无权杀人
but it doesn't give him the right to kill--
不不  天呐  没权利  当然
No. No, no, no. God... God, no! Not the right, that's...
我不是那意思  我是说
That's not what I'm saying. I'm just saying that...
我能理解弗兰克为什么
I can understand why Frank... why...
为什么有人会在经历了那样的失去后
why anyone would seek vengeance for something after...
-想寻求复仇  -不不不
- after losing it-- - Whoa, no, no, no.
这不一样  复仇不是正义
That's not the same. Vengeance is not justice.
他的做法是完全错的
What he's doing is completely wrong.
不管对错  你不能否认这有效
But, right or wrong, you can't deny that it works.
你真那么想吗
You really believe that?
我不知道  不
I don't know. No.
或许吧
Maybe.
不
No, um...
或许  今晚该结束了
You know, maybe this is a good time to call it a night.
我觉得我们都累了
I just think we're both exhausted, and...
这么大的案子  我们...
You know, a case this big, let's just...
嗯  你说得对
Yes, you're probably right.
或许等案子结束了
I don't know, maybe, uh, after... after the trial's over.
-嗯  下次好好约个会  -嗯
- Yeah, a real date next time. - Good.
谢谢
Thanks.
-晚安  -晚安  凯伦
- Uh, good night. - Good night, Karen.
好好休息
Get some rest.
-你偷听了多久  -我没偷听
- How long were you listening? - I wasn't listening.
我没听到任何关于你工作
I didn't hear anything about your work
无聊得让我想系个绞索  套在我脖子上试试的事
that would make me want to tie a noose and test it on my neck.
我就更不提我没听到的关于你女朋友的事了
I won't even mention what I didn't hear about your girlfriend.
我告诉过你别打扰我的生活
I warned you not to interrupt my life.
这才不是你的生活  马修
This is not your life, Matthew.
你或许不在乎我为自己创造的一切
You may not give a damn about what I've made for myself,
但这对我才是最重要的
but that is what's most important to me.
好吗  她对我才是重要的
All right? She... is important to me.
好吧
Right.
抱歉
Sorry.
我不知道你
I didn't know your time
红酒配泰国菜的时间那么重要
pairing wine with Thai food was so important.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
我又仔细查看了罗克森的工程投资
I looked more carefully at Roxxon's construction investment.
在纽约似乎只有几个项目
Seems there's only a small number of projects in New York
会要搬运那么多土
capable of moving that much dirt.
我们去看看  肯定能查明他们想隐藏什么
We pay the sites a visit, I bet we find out what they're hiding.
都在哪
What are these sites?
温室酒店  市中心隧道工程
The Conservatory Hotel, the Midtown Tunnel project,
还有44街和11大道的大型建筑工地
and some big build site at 44th and 11th.
44街和11大道
44th and 11th.
-你知道那里  -中城圈
- You know it? - Yeah, Midland Circle.
那里原来有一栋出租大楼
There was a tenement on that block
但被威尔逊·菲斯克的
before Wilson Fisk swallowed it up
更好明天企划吞并了
in his Better Tomorrow initiative.
-日本人怎么拿到那里的  -我不知道
- How did the Japanese get hold of it? - I don't know.
但我跟信对战之前  发现了中城圈的图纸
But before I fought Nobu, I found blueprints at Midland Circle.
我一直以为信
Now, I always thought Nobu
只是菲斯克派来干掉我的武器
was just a weapon Fisk sent to take me out,
菲斯克在楼盘上有投资
that Fisk had interests tied up in the building,
但或许他根本不需要那栋楼
but maybe he didn't want it at all.
或许他是替日本人收购中城圈的呢
I mean, what if he only acquired Midland Circle for the Japanese?
好有趣的谜语
That's a curious riddle,
我觉得我们该一起去破解
one I think we should go and solve together.
艾丽卡  我明早还要出庭
Elektra, I got court in the morning.
-我得为案子做准备  -那就明晚好了
- I got a case to prepare, I got... - Tomorrow night, then.
廉价酒
Cheap wine.
完成你的作业  我去做侦查
Finish your homework. I'll do some recon.
那么  塔普医生  验尸官办公室
And so, Dr. Tepper, the medical examiner's office
可以确认在爱尔兰俱乐部发现的15具尸体
can confirm that the 15 victims found at the Irish Social Club
都是死于多处枪伤
all died of multiple gunshot wounds.
是的
Yes, that's correct.
全部15名被害人都死于
Um, all 15 victims died of wounds inflicted
同一口径子弹造成的伤
by the same caliber bullet...
每人都身中数枪
each shot multiple times.
谢谢
Thank you.
你方证人
Your witness.
-求上帝保佑吧  -我什么神都求了
- Cross your fingers. - I'm crossing everything.
格莱格里·塔普医生
Dr. Gregory Tepper,
你做纽约市尸检官多久了
how long have you been medical examiner for the city of New York?
14年左右了
Uh, 14 years, uh, give or take.
你估算下你在此期间
And how many death certificates
为多少份死亡证明签过字
would you estimate you've signed in that time?
我不...
Um, I don't, uh...
可能得有个上万份吧
It's probably in the tens of thousands.
反对  法官大人  引导证人
Objection, Your Honor, leading the witness...
-不知所云  -默多克先生
- I'm not sure where. - Mr. Murdock--
我有话得说
I have something I need to say.
-医生  -抱歉  法官大人  但是
- Doctor? - Your Honor, I'm sorry, but...
我必须公开说说
I have to, on the record...
我做的事
I need to say something about what I did.
-清空旁听席  -是  法官大人
- Clear the gallery. - Yes, Your Honor.
陪审团成员全部回到审议室
All jury members, please exit back to the deliberation room.
旁听席上所有人
Everyone in the gallery,
请现在离开法庭
please make your way out of the courtroom at this time.
怎么回事
What's all this about?
我
I...
我知道辩方想问我什么  是真的
I know what the defense was gonna ask me about, and it's true.
我篡改了尸检报告
I altered the autopsy reports.
你是指弗兰克·卡塞尔
Uh, you're referring to the official findings
家人的官方尸检报告吗
on the murders of Frank Castle's family?
不仅如此
Not just them.
你不明白  我必须这么做
You don't understand. I had to do it.
-那些禽兽来过我办公室  -谁
- Those animals came to my office. - Who came to your office?
被告一家被杀后
After the defendant's family was murdered,
两个我没见过的人
two men I'd never seen before...
他们警告我  我如果不修改报告
they warned me, if I didn't fix the case reports,
他们接下来就要杀我的家人
they'd come after my family next.
你篡改了卡塞尔一家的尸检报告
You falsified the autopsy findings on the Castle family?
还有一个人
Them and one more.
-谁  -我不知道
- Who? - I don't know.
是当天另一个被杀的无名氏
Some John Doe killed the same day.
男性  成年人  多处枪伤
Male, adult, multiple gunshot wounds.
你可以解雇我  逮捕我  我不在乎
Look, you can fire me, arrest me... I don't care.
我以为这事都过去了  但是  昨晚
I thought this was behind me, but after last night...
医生  你昨晚遭遇什么影响你证词的事了吗
Doctor, did something happen last night to impact your testimony?
她进了我家
She was in my house.
她把我绑了起来
She tied me up.
她说她不在乎此前是谁找上了我
She said she didn't give a damn who got to me before.
如果我不把事实告诉辩方
If I didn't tell the defense what really happened,
她就会找到我  杀了我
she'd hunt me down and kill me.
-这人是谁  -我不知道
- Who told you this? - I don't know.
一个女人
A woman.
她脸遮住了  操着外国口音
Her face was covered. Had some foreign accent.
法官大人  我认为辩方有意引开陪审团的注意
Your Honor, I believe the defense intends to distract the jury
把案件的重点
and make this case about
转移到无从证明的阴谋论上
some impossible-to-prove conspiracy theories--
无从证明
Impossible to prove?
你的尸检官刚刚确认他篡改了尸检报告
Your ME just confirmed that he doctored the autopsy records.
他还说他遭受了威胁
He also said that he'd been threatened.
如果我部发现
If my office finds out
你们律所跟此事有一点关系
that your firm had anything to do with this--
我们律所  说不定是你派人去恐吓他呢
Our firm? For all we know, it was you who sent those goons.
我听够了
I've heard enough.
显然不管塔普医生
It's clear to me that whatever Dr. Tepper
对尸检报告有什么了解
may know about these autopsy reports
都已经因
has been tainted
一个或数个人的恐吓而无效
by threats made by person or persons unknown.
那么被告请求宣布审判无效
Then the defense asks for a mistrial.
休想  尼尔森先生
Not on your life, Mr. Nelson.
我依然无法确信这些文件
I'm still not convinced these documents,
不管究竟是怎样的  跟本案有关系
whatever they may be, are even relevant to this trial.
我要剔除医生所有的证词
I'm striking the doctor's entire testimony
并将指示陪审团
and instructing the jurors
忘记他们所听到的一切
to disregard anything they may have heard.
法官大人  我强烈敦促...
Your Honor, I strongly urge you to-- -
就这样了  律师
We're done here, counselor.
明天继续开庭
Trial will reconvene tomorrow
检方传唤下一位证人
with the prosecution's next witness.
雷耶斯再次找到了坑我们的新办法
Once again, Reyes finds a new way to screw us.
按理说该越来越好接受  可居然越来越痛苦了
You'd think it'd get easier, but somehow it's more painful.
福吉  福吉  不是雷耶斯
Foggy. Foggy... it wasn't Reyes.
-什么  -威胁塔普的女人
- What? - The woman who threatened Tepper.
是艾丽卡
It was Elektra.
大学那个
From college.
-艾丽卡  -对  她又回来了
- Elektra? - Yeah, she's back in town.
-你的前女友  -对
- Your ex-girlfriend? - Yes.
不可能  太疯狂了
No. This is insane.
她是个外交官的女儿  是个名媛
She's a diplomat's daughter, a... A debutante.
现在不是了  她...
Not anymore. She's, uh...
她变了  她很危险
She's... she's different. She's... she's dangerous.
可不是  她差点害你被开除
Yeah, no shit. She nearly got you expelled.
她坑了你侵权法  民事诉讼的那个学期
I mean, she screwed your semester of torts, civil procedure...
因为她伤你太深  你差点错过期末考
You almost missed the final because she hurt you so bad.
现在怎么
And now, what?
-她又闯入一个验尸官家里了吗  -好吧
- She's... breaking into an ME's house? - Okay.
日本黑帮并没有被消灭
So, the Yakuza didn't go away, all right?
他们还在地狱厨房
They're still here in Hell's Kitchen.
艾丽卡想帮我阻止他们  渗入...
Elektra is trying to help me stop them, infiltrating--
你说什么呢
What are you even talking about?
她本来在自己对抗他们  但她...
She was going up against them by herself, and she--
-你的前女友  -对  我是想保护这个城市
- Your ex-girlfriend? - Yeah, I'm trying to protect the city--
我早知道她疯狂  我不知道她有杀人倾向
I knew she was crazy, I didn't know that she was homicidal.
她
She's, um...
是我的新客户
my new client.
福吉  那个有钱的
Foggy, the, uh... rich one.
我保密的那个
The private one.
-你又撒谎了  -是的
- You lied again. - I did, I lied,
但是日本黑帮在往比之前
but, look, the Yakuza are funneling money into something
更大更黑暗的事里注资
even bigger and darker than before, all right?
艾丽卡来找我  我是想帮她
Elektra came to me, I'm trying to help her--
是你想接这个案子的
You wanted to take this trial!
你不参加策略会议
You missed strategy sessions...
证人准备  开庭陈述  你还违法...
witness prep, opening statements, and you criminally decimate--
不是我  是她
No, I didn't. She...
我没跟她说任何关于审判的事
I never told her anything about the trial, all right?
唯一本能帮忙实现我的目标的证人
The one witness that could've helped us do what I wanted to do,
帮我扳倒雷耶斯
which is take down Reyes!
她肯定是听到我和凯伦的谈话了
She must've overheard me talking to Karen,
便自己采取了行动
and then she moved on her own.
我没让她那么做  我绝不会
I would... I didn't sanction, I would never--
-我不管  马特  -我也气她
- I don't care! I don't care, Matt! - I'm furious with her!
别再装作这些事只是你刚巧碰上
Stop acting like these things just happen to you!
没人逼你大晚上
No one's making you go out
整宿不睡去对付坏人
all hours of the night fighting bad guys
也没人逼你反复对你的朋友撒谎
and nobody makes you lie to your friends, over and over again!
艾丽卡不是问题所在  马特
Elektra is not the problem, Matt.
你才是
You are.
快天黑了
It's almost dark.
你肯定还有地方要去
I'm sure there's someplace you gotta be-- -
你别走
You're not walking away.
-不  告诉你  -别就这么走  福吉
- No, 'cause you know what? - Don't walk away from me, Foggy.
从过去几天来看
If the last few days are any indication,
你的心根本不在这里
you sure as hell haven't been here!
今后  我再不会指望你什么了
Going forward, I will count on you for nothing at all.
叫你女朋友别插手我的案子
Tell your girlfriend to stay away from my trial.
她不是  艾丽卡不是我的女朋友
Yeah, she's not... Elektra's not my girlfriend.
那你去告诉凯伦她的事吧
Then you should be the one to tell Karen about her.
-我听到了吼声  -嗯  你去跟马特说吧
- Hey, I heard yelling. - Yeah, you should talk to Matt about it.
福吉
Foggy!
-刚刚怎么回事  -我们没事
- Hey, what the hell happened in there? - We're fine.
不不  别拿我当秘书
No, no, no, you don't treat me like I'm just your secretary.
我在这案子上付出的比你还多
I've done more work on this case than you have!
我现在没法说  凯伦
I can't get into this right now, Karen.
不  你别再躲躲闪闪了
No, enough of the dodgy bullshit.
我有权知道你俩是怎么回事
I deserve to know what is going on with you two.
你是怎么回事
With you.
你是作为同事问我这话吗
You asking as my co-worker?
还是我女朋友
Or my girlfriend?
-都是  -好吧
- Both. - Yeah.
对不起你被卷了进来
I am sorry you're caught in the middle of this,
但我现在得走了
but right now, I have to go.
-你去哪  -我们明天见  凯伦
- Where? - I'll see you tomorrow, Karen.
或许吧
Yeah, maybe.
你做了什么  我叫你远离我的生活
What the hell did you do? I told you to stay out of my life.
我没叫你去强迫证人
I never asked you to coerce a witness!
你有个问题  所以我插手了
You had a problem, so I stepped in.
不  你没帮忙
No! It doesn't help.
因为你  我们不能用他的证词了
We can't even use his testimony because of you.
都被剔除了
It was all thrown out.
我不过是遵循了你的规矩
I was only following your rules.
-什么规矩  -白天你是得不到你想要的
- What rules? - You don't get what you want by day.
只能晚上靠武力夺来
You take it by force at night.
这就是真实的你  马修
This is who you are, Matthew.
别骗自己不是这样
And don't fool yourself into thinking it's anything else.
我做什么
What I do...
与你无关
is none of your business.
-我的两部分生活都是我自己的  -好吧
- Both halves of my life are mine. - Fine.
我不会再插手你无聊的法律事务
I'll stay out of your boring legal shit.
你想跟我打一架
Now, you wanna fight me?
还是去打那些破坏你城市的人
Or you wanna fight the guys who are tearing your city apart?
-你不想帮忙吗  -你不想我帮忙
- You didn't wanna help? - You didn't want me to.
准备好了吗
Ready?
有动静吗
You hear something?
没有别人
We're alone.
空的  这里面什么都没有
It's empty. There's nothing in here.
-日本黑帮肯定是在守护什么  -是啊  但是
- The Yakuza were guarding something. - Yeah, but...
-艾丽卡  -怎么了
- Elektra. - What?
你不会相信的
You're not gonna believe this.
老天爷
Holy shit.
日本黑帮为什么要挖大坑
Why are the Yakuza digging a hole?
手电筒给我
Give me the flashlight.
-到底了吗  -没有
- Did it hit the bottom? - No.
到底告诉我
Tell me when it does.